<section xml:id="HW-dimension">
      <title>HW: Dimension and Definition</title>
      
      <p>
       We have now seen the dimension of fractals and of vector spaces. 
       Mathematician and author, David Richeson, explored the concept of dimension 
       further in amazing Quanta Magazine article: "The Journey to Define Dimension" \cite{richeson}.
      </p>  

      <question xml:id="q-richeson">
        <title>Quanta Magazine's The Journey to Defining Dimension</title>
        <statement>
        <p>
            Read David Richeson’s article <url href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/a-mathematicians-guided-tour-through-high-dimensions-20210913/" visual="The Journey to Defining Dimension">"The Journey to Defining Dimension".</url> 
          <xref ref="biblio-richeson"/>
        </p>
        </statement>
       </question>
       
       
       <question xml:id="q-richeson-q1">
        <statement>
        <p>
         Describe what we would observe if a 4-dimensional sphere collided with our 3-dimensional space.
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-richeson-q2">
        <statement>
        <p>
        List four people mentioned in this article and their contribution to the discussion of dimension.
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-richeson-q3">
        <statement>
        <p>
        Georg Cantor talked about the cardinality of infinity. What does he mean by "cardinality”?
         Explain what Cantor was referring to when he said, "I see it, but I do not believe it.”
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-richeson-q4">
        <statement>
        <p>
        How did Hausdorff define dimension? What mathematical concept came from his definition?
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <subsection xml:id="quanta-magazine">
          <title>Quanta Magazine</title>
        </subsection>

        <p>
        Quanta Magazine is an editorially independent online publication launched by the Simons Foundation in 2012 
        to enhance public understanding of science. In their own words, 'Why Quanta? Albert Einstein called photons
         “quanta of light.” Our goal is to “illuminate science.”'
        </p>

        <p>
        Quanta Magazine offers a lot of interesting high-level content in the 
        sciences and mathematics completely for free. They have won multiple journalism awards
        including the 2022 Pulitzer Prize for Explanatory Reporting.</p>

        <question xml:id="q-quanta-q1">
        <statement>
        <p>
         Find an article from Quanta Magazine that is interesting to you, 
         and post a link to it in the Canvas discussino post "Quanta Magazine".
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

       

    </section>