<section xml:id="HW-mengersponge">
      <title>HW: Menger Sponge and the Mandlebrot Set</title>
      
      <p>
      Let's get back to fractals. There are several famous fractals of interest. We already saw Sierpinski's Triangle. 
       Another one of these is the Menger Sponge.
      </p>

      <figure>
        <image source="images/menger" width="50%"/>
      </figure>

      <subsection xml:id="my-favorite-spaces">
        <title>A Few of My Favorite Spaces</title>

        <p>
        Mathematician Evelyn Lamb has written as an incredible series entitled "A Few of My Favorite Space" 
        for Scientific American covering different mathematical spaces.
        </p>

        <question xml:id="q-menger-sponge1">
        <title>The Menger Sponge</title>
        <statement>
        <p>
          Read Evelyn Lamb's article <url href="https://blogs.scientificamerican.com/roots-of-unity/a-few-of-my-favorite-spaces-the-menger-sponge/" visual="A Few of My Favorite Spaces: The Menger Sponge">"A Few of My Favorite Spaces: The Menger Sponge".</url> 
          <xref ref="biblio-menger"/>
        </p>
        </statement>
       </question>
    
        <p>
        What did you think about Lamb's article? Answer the following questions after reading it.
        </p>

        <question xml:id="q-menger-q2">
        <statement>
        <p>
         How do you develop the Menger Sponge?
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-menger-q3">
        <statement>
        <p>
         What is the dimension of the Menger Sponge?
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-menger-q4">
        <statement>
        <p>
         What are your thoughts about the Menger Sponge?
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>
        
      </subsection>     

      <subsection xml:id ="mandelbrot">
        <title>The Mandelbrot Set and Numberphile</title>

        <p>
        Another famous fractal is the Mandelbrot Set shown in Figure
        </p>

        <p>
        Numberphile is a popular math-related YouTube channel that covers a huge
         variety interesting high-level mathematics topics. Numberphile is a channel you should bookmark
         as a young math student. We will look to Numberphile several times in this text, but we're pretty sure you'll
         stay up late binging their videos.
        
            <figure>
                <caption>The Mandlebrot Set- Numberphile</caption>
                <video xml:id="sphere-inversion" youtube="NGMRB4O922I" />
            </figure> 
        </p>

      <question xml:id="q-mandlebrot-q1">
        <statement>
        <p>
         Explain the process that determines whether or not a number will be in the Mandelbrot Set or not.
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>
      
      </subsection>     
       
       

       <p>
         MIT's Origami Club, OragMIT, built Menger Sponges from business cards! We should do this.
      <figure>
        <caption>Building the Menger Sponge</caption>
        <video xml:id="menger-video" youtube="YpmP8OJJ7W4" />
      </figure> 
      </p>

    </section>