<section xml:id="HW-pascal">
      <title>HW: Pascal's Triangle</title>
      
      <p>
      Pascal's Triangle is an easy construction that has a variety of interesting patterns and applications. 
      Pascal's Triangle is named after mathematician Blaise Pascal, considered the father of Probability Theory.
      Pascal used Pascal's Triangle to calculate binomial probability, but the triangle was known and in use other 
      parts of the world centuries before Pascal.
      </p>

      <figure>
        <image source="images/pascal_triangle.png" width="50%"/>
      </figure>

      <subsection xml:id="mathigon-pascals">
        <title>Mathigon and Pascal's Triangle</title>

        <p>
        Mathigon is a fantastic and quickly-growing resource for mathematics. There goal is offer 
        free tools, courses and manipulatives to make online learning more interactive and engaging than before. 
        We will take now look at a section of one of Mathigon's courses "Sequences and Patterns".
        </p>

        <p>
        From <url href="https://mathigon.org/course/sequences/pascals-triangle" visual="Mathigon">"Mathigon".</url>, we
        can work through a colorful, interactive course. Work through Mathigon's Pascal's Triangle and answer the 
        following questions.
        </p>

        <question xml:id="q-pascal-q1">
        <statement>
        <p>
         Write out the first 8 rows of Pascal’s Triangle.
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-pascal-q2">
        <statement>
        <p>
         What patterns show up in the first four diagonals?
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-pascal-q3">
        <statement>
        <p>
         What numbers show up by adding entries of a given row of Pascal’s Triangle?
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-pascal-q4">
        <statement>
        <p>
         Describe how the Fibonacci sequence is encoded into Pascal’s Triangle.
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-pascal-q5">
        <statement>
        <p>
         What does mathematician David Singmaster conjecture?
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-pascal-q6">
        <statement>
        <p>
         What fractal is connected to Pascal's triangle?
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>


      </subsection>

      <subsection xml:id="pascals-counting">
        <title>Pascal's Triangle and Counting</title>

        <p>
        Blaise Pascal's interest in Pascal's Triangle was actually related to counting. MathisFun.com shares a lot of 
        interesting mathematical concepts including Pascal`s Triangle. Answer the following questions using MathisFun.com's
        <url href="https://www.mathsisfun.com/pascals-triangle.html" visual="Pascal's Triangle">"Pascal's Triangle".</url> article. <xref ref="biblio-mathisfun"/>
                
        </p>   

        <question xml:id="q-pascal2-q1">
        <statement>
        <p>
          Use Pascal’s Triangle to find <m>11^8</m>.
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-pascal2-q2">
        <statement>
        <p>
          If you flip a coin 5 times, in how many different ways can you flip 3 heads? Use Pascal’s Triangle to solve.
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-pascal2-q3">
        <statement>
        <p>
         Pascal’s Triangle can help count combinations. Use Pascal’s Triangle to deduce the number of 
         ways we can select 5 objects out of 8.
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-pascal2-q4">
         <statement>
         <p>
          Use Pascal’s Triangle to expand <m>(x+y)^7</m>.
         </p>
         </statement>
        </question>        
      </subsection>     

    </section>