<section xml:id="HW-pascal">
      <title>HW: Pascal's Triangle</title>
      
      <p>
      Pascal's Triangle is an easy construction that has a variety of interesting patterns and applications. 
      Pascal's Triangle is named after mathematician Blaise Pascal, considered the father of Probability Theory.
      Pascal used Pascal's Triangle to calculate binomial probability, but the triangle was known and in use other 
      parts of the world centuries before Pascal.
      </p>

      <figure>
        <image source="images/pascal_triangle.png" width="50%"/>
      </figure>

      <subsection xml:id="mathigon-pascals">
        <title>Mathigon and Pascal's Triangle</title>

        <p>
        Mathigon is a fantastic and quickly-growing resource for mathematics. There goal is offer 
        free tools, courses and manipulatives to make online learning more interactive and engaging than before. 
        We will take now look at a section of one of Mathigon's courses "Sequences and Patterns".
        </p>

        <p>
        From <url href="https://mathigon.org/course/sequences/pascals-triangle" visual="Mathigon">"Mathigon".</url>, we
        can work through a colorful, interactive course. Work through Mathigon's Pascal's Triangle and answer the 
        following questions.
        </p>

        <question xml:id="q-pascal-q1">
        <statement>
        <p>
         Write out the first 8 rows of Pascal’s Triangle.
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-pascal-q2">
        <statement>
        <p>
         What patterns show up in the first four diagonals?
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-pascal-q3">
        <statement>
        <p>
         What numbers show up by adding entries of a given row of Pascal’s Triangle?
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-pascal-q4">
        <statement>
        <p>
         Describe how the Fibonacci sequence is encoded into Pascal’s Triangle.
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-pascal-q5">
        <statement>
        <p>
         What does mathematician David Singmaster conjecture?
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-pascal-q6">
        <statement>
        <p>
         What fractal is connected to Pascal's triangle?
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>


      </subsection>

      <subsection xml:id="pascals-counting">
        <title>Pascal's Triangle and Counting</title>

        <p>
        Mathematician Evelyn Lamb has written as an incredible series entitled "A Few of My Favorite Space" 
        for Scientific American covering different mathematical spaces.
        </p>

        <question xml:id="q-menger-sponge1">
        <title>The Menger Sponge</title>
        <statement>
        <p>
          Read Evelyn Lamb's article <url href="https://blogs.scientificamerican.com/roots-of-unity/a-few-of-my-favorite-spaces-the-menger-sponge/" visual="A Few of My Favorite Spaces: The Menger Sponge">"A Few of My Favorite Spaces: The Menger Sponge".</url> 
          <xref ref="biblio-menger"/>
        </p>
        </statement>
       </question>
    
        <p>
        What did you think about Lamb's article? Answer the following questions after reading it.
        </p>

        <question xml:id="q-menger-q2">
        <statement>
        <p>
         How do you develop the Menger Sponge?
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-menger-q3">
        <statement>
        <p>
         What is the dimension of the Menger Sponge?
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>

        <question xml:id="q-menger-q4">
        <statement>
        <p>
         What are your thoughts about the Menger Sponge?
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>
        
      </subsection>     

      <subsection xml:id ="mandelbrot">
        <title>The Mandelbrot Set and Numberphile</title>

        <p>
        Another famous fractal is the Mandelbrot Set shown in Figure
        </p>

        <p>
        Numberphile is a popular math-related YouTube channel that covers a huge
         variety interesting high-level mathematics topics. Numberphile is a channel you should bookmark
         as a young math student. We will look to Numberphile several times in this text, but we're pretty sure you'll
         stay up late binging their videos.
        
            <figure>
                <caption>The Mandlebrot Set- Numberphile</caption>
                <video xml:id="sphere-inversion" youtube="NGMRB4O922I" />
            </figure> 
        </p>

      <question xml:id="q-mandlebrot-q1">
        <statement>
        <p>
         Explain the process that determines whether or not a number will be in the Mandelbrot Set or not.
        </p>
        </statement>
        </question>
      
      </subsection>     
       
       

       <p>
         MIT's Origami Club, OragMIT, built Menger Sponges from business cards! We should do this.
      <figure>
        <caption>Building the Menger Sponge</caption>
        <video xml:id="menger-video" youtube="YpmP8OJJ7W4" />
      </figure> 
      </p>

    </section>