    <section xml:id="belhaven-community">
      <title>More on the Belhaven MCS Community</title>
      
      <p>
        We mentioned already the key pillars of the Belhaven MCS Department. Now we want to dig into those
        with a bit more attetion. As part of the Belhaven Division of Natural Science (Belhaven STEM), the MCS Department
        provides a number of opportunities we feel develop critical thinking, professionalism, and vision for the future. However,
        we also want you to feel supported and encouraged. 
      </p>

      <p>Remember the Belhaven MCS mission statement? <term>I pursue my career and calling through community, 
      academic experiences, and technology</term>. We will look at each of these pillars. Let's start with community.</p>

      <subsection xml:id="subsec-community">
      <title>Community</title>
      <p>
      "It's not what you know, but who you know." We don't exactly prescribe this adage as a hard and fast rule, BUT... it 
      knowing the right people can be very powerful. Young students do not always understand how valuable community can be, but
      we picked community as our first pillar for a reason.
      </p>

      <p>We want you to be a part of something special! While we provide opportunities for you, it's up to you to
      take advantage of them. What can you do to quickly join our community? Great question!
      </p>
      <p>(Join the BelhavenSTEM Team :). )</p>
      </subsection>

      <!-- MCS Club, social events, maker campus -->
      <subsection xml:id="subsec-mcsclub">
      <title>MCS Club</title>
      <p>
      The student-led MCS Club. 
      </p>

      </subsection>

      <subsection xml:id="subsec-social">
      <title>Division Social Events</title>
      <p> 
      The MCS Department and the Division of Natural Science host a variety of events for students.  
      <ul>
        <li> </li>
      </ul>
      </p>

      </subsection>

      <subsection xml:id="subsec-makercampus">
      <title>Belhaven Maker Campus</title>
      <p> 
      </p>

      </subsection>

    </section>
